Visit our website for more: turkision.com
No living being was harmed during
the filming of this series.
Episode 120
Your soul and blood are mine, Osman.
You will die.
Dying is hard, but killing is easy.
Come and see.
Come here.
Wait.
Now!
O Allah!
Attack!
You, Nayman!
With this wounded hand, you can't
even graze a sheep, son of Osman.
Will you kill me with it?
Attack me while you have the chance.
You may not have
the chance anymore.
You are brave, but courage is not enough.
You are weak, Orhan.
I am strong as I can
take your breath away.
Your strength is not
enough to defeat me.
But I am the one
who can give you strength.
I don't want anything from you.
The only thing I will take
from you is your life.
My hands will heal in time.
Nayman is greater than time.
Fire Turkish arrows at
the chests of the infidels!
Mashallah!
If you want to find medicine,
you must come to my camp.
What is happening?
Who is this man?
Come on, they are
waiting for you at the palace.
You go brother, I have some work
to do.
Be careful, brother, don't be late.
I'll come in time, you go.
We fall to the ground for our calling...
...but you...
Your death is in vain.
Come here.
Come here
Sit here.
Nayman will send you
to the bottom of the earth!
And Nayman will come to you soon.
Then you ask him if he killed me or not.
Come here, get up.
We will all die.
However, Erlik Khan...
All of us.
But our only wish is that
the dust we fall upon becomes our home.
May it be a home for us
to make it a shield for the oppressed.
But we will not allow
people like you to breathe.
It's time.
Allah is the greatest!
O Allah.
Öktem tribe
What's on your mind, mother?
It hasn't been forty
days since my father's death.
Why are you asking for
a wedding so quickly?
Your father's absence burns my soul too.
The deceased was not just your father.
Rather, he was my husband, the Bey
of my tribe, and the pillar of my tent.
My heart aches too.
Does your heart ache like this way?
Speaking of the wedding?
You said what you
said, so let me say it too.
The wedding will not take
place until my mourning is over.
Do I care about the wedding
or feast, Alçiçek?
But the marriage will happen.
It needs to be done.
Don't you still
understand why I do this?
Look at this chair well
Beys are silent now that I sit on it.
But when our pain subsides, they
will strongly object to that.
You...
I'll make Aktemur sit on the chair before
Beys object to my sitting on it.
Aktemur?
But he will not accept.
He's the Subasi in Yenişehir.
He will accept, we have
no other solution.
If Aktemur doesn't sit on the it, forget
about the Kargın tribe, my daughter.
If I knew Aktemur even a little bit,
he wouldn't accept it.
He will.
Are you the woman he loves?
You will convince him.
How am I going to do this?
Alçiçek, use your brain, daughter.
You can make him do
anything you ask him to do.
But know that this is not for me.
And not for yourself.
Rather, you will do it to preserve our
tribe, your father's trust in us.
Go talk to Aktemur now.
Yenişehir
Bengi Hatun wants to make
Aktemur the Bey of her tribe.
What do you say, Bala?
Who said this?
No one needs to say anything
Why do you think Bengi wants
the marriage quickly?
Doesn't she sit on the
seat of sovereignty?
Why does she want to make Aktemur
Bey sit on it? I don't understand.
Also, there is a period of
mourning for her husband.
What makes sense to do such a thing?
Bengi.
She is well-calculated.
She knows very well that the Beys will
revolt when the mourning is over.
Yes.
She wants to get Aktemur to
sit before the Beys revolt.
She will make Aktemur a Beys
and use it as she pleases.
No.
Aktemur will never allow this.
No!
Aktemur is a smart man.
And he knows he shouldn't do
anything without Osman Bey's permission.
However...
Aktemur is also a kind person.
May his mercy not drag
him into wrongdoing.
I'm not going to let her take
advantage of my son, Malhun.
She can't make Atktemur sit on the seat of
sovereignty and use him as she pleases.
I will not allow her.
Alçiçek won't allow this.
Let's pray she won't be
complacent with this.
What's more important than the words
and approval of others...
is what Osman Bey will say
when we tell him
- Boran.
- My Bey.
Send half of the Alps to Yenişehir...
and increase the measures.
Obviously, Nayman wouldn't sit still.
Your command, my Bey.
- Turgut Bey.
- Yes, Osman Bey.
Send Alps to and around İnegöl.
Nayman will think we died here.
He will try to attack
our property.
Alps never lose sight in İnegöl.
Don't worry.
What should we do now, my Bey?
We will go to Söğüt.
My Bey.
What are we going to do
with these soldiers?
Take them and put
them in the cart.
Put them in the cart and
send them to their owner.
And fill their mouths with dirt.
Fill it in to see the fate of
those who covet our lands.
Come on.
Your command, my Bey.
Drom where is this?
I do not want a foreign work, but
rather a Turkish work.
We don't have any foreign work.
It is a Turkish work made
by the neighboring tribes.
No, not this.
I want the best.
I am preparing a dowry for my daughter.
Well, take your pick and prepare.
Send these to the palace of Osman Bey.
Osman Bey's palace?
Yes.
Who are you, Hatun?
That's none of your business.
Do your job.
They say curiosity kills a man,
don't you know that?
Excuse me, I was surprised when
you said "Osman Bey's palace."
What am I going to do now, Kumral Abdal?
How am I going to make
things up with Ülgen Hatun?
Your treatment is there.
Come on, get your money bag out.
Come on.
What do I do with the bag?
Shall I give her money?
Of course, you will not go empty-handed
to ask for her forgiveness.
Shop.
Come on, to the shop.
Thank you, Kumral Abdal!
Look at me.
Yes?
Do you have another color?
Here, on this side, there
is also the color red.
Give it to me, young man.
I caught it
first, don't take offense.
It's mine and you
should pick from other fabrics.
I need a red cloth.
Leave it!
Oh my!
I told you I caught it first, grandmother.
This cloth is mine, don't be
stubborn, it's important!
Cerkutay!
Leave it, choose another fabric.
What you are doing is
disgraceful to the Hatun.
Is that a disgrace to her
and not a disgrace to me?
I said I had it first!
Leave it!
You leave it!
Leave him, you damned!
Leave it! I hope your head cracks!
I will not leave it, if you leave it, you will fall.
Also, I need this cloth.
Leave it, I took it.
You lunatic!
I will spill your blood!
Cerkutay.
It can't be, Alçiçek.
I am the Subasi of Yenişehir.
I do not covet sovereignty.
Also, isn't there any man in this
large tribe to be the Bey?
Do I have a brother to hide
from you, Aktemur?
I don't have, don't you know?
Only my mother and I are here.
And we have no one else.
We don't.
We are alone.
You know I didn't mean to say that.
I am always by your side.
But I do not follow sovereignty.
This is not an issue of sovereignty.
Rather, it is an emergency.
Our tribe is my father's trust in us.
Will you not keep this trust?
Also...
Beys of the tribe will not accept this.
If you accept, the rest
doesn't matter to anyone.
My mother will speak to the Beys.
We don't have anyone as
good as you to be a Bey.
There is no place in our tribe for a Bey who doesn't pledge allegiance to the son of Gündüz Bey.
Do you think you can't do that?
Or are you afraid?
What am I afraid of, Alçiçek?
I am not afraid.
However, Osman Bey...
What does my uncle think about this?
I cannot do this
without consulting him.
But you're in a hurry.
You're leaving me stuck
between you two, Alçiçek.
Osman Bey left the
great Yenişehir as a trust to you.
Why would he be against you being
the Bey of the Kargın tribe?
The Kargın tribe is also related to the Kayı.
But if you do not accept this trust...
my tribe will perish
and disappear, Aktemur.
I never liked this, Alçiçek.
We have to.
We have to, Aktemur.
My mother is sitting on the chair now.
However, Beys will begin to disobey soon.
You're not going to sacrifice
your position in this mess, are you?
You're going to sit in the chair, right?
You hit me.
You hit Cerkutay.
Whoa, whoa.
Who will take you from my hands now?
Come here!
Stop, Hatun, stop!
Will you hit him with a sword?
Stop!
Go away!
Give it to me!
Pray to Allah that you are not a man!
I ignore this behavior of yours because
your old age, grandmother.
Cerkutay.
Come over here!
Stop, sister, stop, stop!
You don't know.
He's crazy.
What?
Are you telling the truth?
Yes.
He's crazy.
This is good, otherwise, I would
kill him.
Okay then.
You saved me from committing a great sin.
Otherwise, I wouldn't have cared that he was crazy
and would have knocked him to the ground!
I think I know you...
Kumral Abdal.
This is you, right?
You...
You are...
The brown midwife.
Feriştah Hatun?
Where is Osman's head?
Osman!
He escaped the trap we
set, Commander Nayman.
We didn't do it ourselves.
He survived!
Where is Gök Talay?
Osman...
Gök Talay's head...
You weren't the only arrow I shot.
Osman.
He will come.
Söğüt
Celali.
Are you the one who sold me?
What are you saying?
Bayındır...
Since when does a dog do something without
its owner's knowledge, Mother Sultan?
The dog remains a dog.
His devotion is to himself only.
We see his sincerity as long as we
benefit him, Osman Bey.
Apparently, Nayman gave him more bone.
However, I will kill Bayındır!
Say, what did he give him?
Mashallah!
Slowly, slowly!
These goods will go a long way.
Move carefully.
Hüseyin.
I will be very rich, Hüseyin.
After I set up Osman...
there's no one
better than me for Nayman.
It is true what you say.
Genghis Khan's charter is
in my possession.
Let's get out on the road..
and take
these goods beyond the border areas.
And then you will see that
everyone will kneel before me.
There will be no ruling
left for İsmihan or Osman.
I will not hear from any of them.
Shall we go at once, my bey?
Yes.
It won't take long for İsmihan to find
out what we're weaving here.
Well, what about Osman?
If he escaped from the trap?
What did we do, Hüseyin?
We did our job.
And we got our reward.
I have to see Nayman before we go.
Come on.
I said what does he have?
A charter.
A charter that Genghis Khan
gave to merchants...
so that they could move
between regions within his lands.
This is not something
that can be given to anyone.
You think of the value of your head, Osman Bey.
But this is not important.
I'll kill Bayındır as soon as possible.
No.
Bayındır will live a while.
Will you pardon his betrayal, Osman Bey?
You say that what he has enables him to
go from one area to another.
We need the charter.
And Bayındır.
Why?
To succeed first.
Then, you will hear the reason with
everyone, Mother Sultan.
She is not a woman but a beast.
How did she hit my head?
Her hand is very strong.
What are you looking at?
Wise people can't find me!
Cerkutay!
What did you do?
It is nothing.
I met a grandmother like
a monster in the market.
And what?
And...
It seems that she knew that I made you
sad, so she spilled my blood.
Yes, correct.
She did a good job.
Good.
Stop it, Ülgen.
Ülgen Hatun.
A little time left for iftaar.
I'll prepare the food, don't distract me.
I don't distract you, I don't
distract you.
Is this for me?
Yes.
Do you like it?
It's very beautiful, I like it.
But if you think I'll forgive you
for a piece of cloth, you're wrong...
Cerkutay Alp.
It is not an ordinary cloth.
I argued with a monster for this cloth.
I shed blood.
Yes.
That damned man!
That wild woman hit my head so hard...
that I can still hear her voice!
Mother!
Oh man!
The brown midwife, Feriştah.
Monster.
- Is she your mother?
- Yes.
Oh my.
Ülgen!
Why do you stand like a tree?
Come and take what's in my hand.
Yes.
Mother?
My little girl!
I missed you.
Come on, mother.
What is this lunatic doing here?
- Lunatic?
Yes, he's crazy.
Mother, he's crazy walking around here.
Come on, let's go inside.
What does crazy mean?
I said that unintentionally.
Cloth.
The brown midwife Feriştah.
You're done, Cerkutay.
You're done.
I'm done.
Yes, he is not in the palace either.
So, where is this boy?
Malhun.
Aladdin is the last person to see Orhan.
My brother was talking to a dervish.
Who is that dervish?
Then I said, let's go back
to the palace, and he said no.
I reminded him of Kumral Abdal and
the importance of timing his medication.
He said, "don't worry, I'll come in time."
I was going to look at his hand.
I mean, I don't want to cause anxiety...
he would come, Malhun Hatun.
Who is that dervish, my son?
Didn't you see him?
No, my brother spoke to him.
I asked him and he said he
was asking about the way.
I wish I hadn't left him alone.
Malhun, don't worry.
The condition of his hand
disturbs him greatly.
He clearly wants to practice on his own.
You say so, however...
even when he went to training,
he wouldn't go without my knowledge, Bala.
I sent news to the warriors, we
will find him.
Inshallah.
Commander Nayman.
Orhan is here.
Welcome, son of Osman.
I came to see if you were a man
of his word, Nayman.
Can you treat my hand?
Konur, take several warriors with you.
When you meet with Turgut Bey
and his warriors, give him this.
Your command, my Bey.
Bayındır is with Nayman.
You will track him down.
You will know every step he takes,
you will know all his campaigns.
My Bey, what is our purpose
in tracking him?
Bayıdır is betraying us.
As there is good in every evil, it
will benefit us.
Come on, everyone back to work, we're
going to Yenişehir.
You will recover, son of Osman.
We take good from all evil, Nayman.
Be the reason for my recovery.
May my healing be the reason
for our friendship.
No doubt, it will be done.
Doubt is necessary.
My body is healed.
But what about my hands?
So, you make me need you?
So, I come here?
Say it.
You are brave, but you are fools.
Shall we carry him to the
tent, Commander Nayman?
They consider themselves wolves...
extreme cold heals wolves.
He will survive in extreme cold.
He will heal.
Commander Nayman.
Bayındır and Vizier Saveli are here.
Let them come.
Commander Nayman.
What is Orhan doing here?
Don't you dare...
I heard that Osman is not dead and
that his son is sleeping here.
Is your intention to make him kill me?
Don't get caught up in
these things, merchant.
You proved your loyalty by exposing
the game Osman set up for me.
Your loyalty saves your soul.
You passed the exam.
You will be rewarded.
You have given me the biggest reward.
The gift of the great
Nayman cannot be returned.
However...
Don't check your stuff in vain, merchant.
It's fake.
It's not Genghis Khan's document.
Not?
No.
If you took it out on the road...
The first soldier to show it
would have cut your throat.
You will take this document.
You'll give it to Talay and take the seal.
Seal?
Will the document not become
mine?
All Mongols will unite under my shadow
when you bring that seal.
No need for money.
You'll get rich, anyway,
when I'm in charge.
Yes, and what about Osman?
If Osman is after the seal...
your money will only keep the Mongol
soldiers out of my way, not Osman's.
You will unite with my soldiers at
the position of Akçaağaç.
Then no one will stand in your way.
Yenişehir
Osman.
What happened, Malhun?
Is there bad news?
Orhan is missing.
No one has seen my son.
Where would he have gone in that state?
What is he doing?
We sent warriors to the vicinity
of Yenişehir, but no one saw him.
Aladdin is the last person to see him,
and he was talking to a dervish.
You didn't find him anywhere, did you?
Or do you know where he is?
Orhan is on a mission.
Alhamdulillah, we worried about him a lot
If that's the case, why don't you tell us?
Besides, what kind of mission
are you hiding even from us?
Don't get upset.
Don't be upset.
I have also recently learned about it.
My Bey, there is a knight coming.
Orhan.
My Bey.
Son, are you okay?
Nayman met me today in Yenişehir.
What are you saying?
Are you well?
I'm fine, father.
Nayman says he'll fix my hand.
What?
He says he will treat me if
I go to his camp.
I want recovery more than anything else.
But what I want most...
What do you want?
Son, say it.
What do you want the most?
If you are paralyzed or lame...
those don't prevent us from
becoming a great country.
But if I go to Nayman
and put you in a tough spot...
May your heart always
beat with this calling.
Then your body will heal and the
world will become our home too.
Look.
Son.
It's your mission now.
But you will open your
eyes and ears very well.
May your conquest be blessed.
May you be blessed,my Bey.
He's going to Nayman.
Nayman will fix his arm.
What are you saying, Osman?
We couldn't know what that dog would do.
How could you allow something like that?
Malhun is right.
- What if he did something to Orhan?
- No.
Nayman can't do anything to him.
What are you going to do with Orhan?
Since he's here, you must have a plan.
Let's kill him and finish
him off, Commander Nayman.
What can this boy do for us?
No.
This will be the last example of my mercy.
He will live.
He will receive treatment.
A hungry dog ​​bites its owner.
First, you will fill your belly...
and later...
I will explain your task to you
step by step.
Come on.
Enter the tent.
Thank you, Commander Natman, but...
I am fasting.
You know your gold won't
save you in the afterlife.
Come in, Bayındır.
We have surrounded the
headquarters from all sides.
As Osman Bey said...
if the opposite
happens, we will support them.
We'll take Orhan Bey out, brothers.
Doesn't Osman Bey
fear for the lives of his children?
A wolf that does not have a scar
on its neck is not considered a wolf.
You're right, Aykurt.
You say you took every precaution.
Well, what about Nayman?
What does he want from Orhan?
He treated him first and now, he
is completing what he did.
So what does he want?
He wants Orhan for the same reason
he wants me.
His intention isn't to diminish the
number of those who are against him.
Rather, to increase the
number of those in his class.
He couldn't bring me to his side and
now he wants to take advantage of Orhan.
And what do you want, my Bey?
Orhan will open his ears and eyes well.
I know part of Nayman's plan.
And Orhan will do the rest.
Just as the buds of our country are
transformed into a mighty tree.
What you say is nice, however...
What if something worse
happened to Orhan?
Tell me.
When I was at Nayman's headquarters...
Were you both freaking out like that?
They treated Orhan the same way.
Since he will follow the
example of his ancestors...
Orhan will also walk the
thorny paths that we passed.
Don't worry.
He will come back safely.
Like the wolf attacks the lamb...
he will attack and get
out of there safely.
And now...
there is another...
important thing.
Tell Bengi Hatun and ask her to come.
Let's have iftaar together.
And let's talk about the
thing that is incomplete.
Come on.
You and those with you will ask
my father for mercy, Nayman.
Hurry up.
We'll load it all into Bayındır's cart.
Come on!
Söğüt
Bayındır!
He had the courage to betray me.
What is the penalty for betraying me...
Celali?
To lose what he loves most, Mother Sultan.
I'll catch him.
First I'll take the document
from his hand...
and then...
his money...
and then....
his life.
As long as he has armor like Nayman...
catching him
certainly won't be easy.
However, I will do something that...
What shall we do, Mother Sultan?
Allah is great!
First, we will break our fast, Celali.
I bear witness that there
is no deity but Allah...
Yenişehir, Osman Bey's palace.
I bear witness that there
is no deity but Allah...
In the name of Allah, the most
gracious, the most merciful.
O Possessor of majesty and honor.
We thank you for getting us to have
the blessed Ramadan.
Amin.
We know that prayers come from
fasting mouths at the iftaar table...
is important.
Oh my Allah, the Most
Gracious, the Most Merciful.
Unite all Muslims under
the banner of Islam.
Amin.
Make us the back on which the oppressed rely
and the city that terrorizes the oppressors!
Amin.
We are powerless.
Get us together.
Heal all our diseases that
are in our bodies and souls.
Amin.
Oh my Allah.
In the blessed Ramadan, all devils are chained up.
But our souls are with us.
Save us from obeying ourselves
and indulging in sin.
Amin.
Grant us good obedience in Ramadan,
and let us reach Eid with goodness.
Amin.
May Allah accept our fasts.
Come on, enjoy your meal.
In the name of Allah, the most
gracious, the most merciful.
Go ahead.
In the name of Allah, the most
gracious, the most merciful.
Oh.
Praise be to Allah, thank you very much.
We broke our fast.
Thank Allah that my son did his job
and made it to our iftaar.
As we broke our fasts....
tell us, son.
What's happening in Nayman's around?
My Bey.
What I heard and saw
hurt my soul.
Those who are on our
side are betraying us.
Bayındır Bey.
What's his campaign?
Bayındır Bey will go to
Talay to take the seal.
Soldiers will unite in Akçaağaç.
If Nayman has the seal...
he will put it on our death firman.
Never worry, we won't allow that.
Bayindir only cares about the gold.
This is expected of him.
...but Vizier Saveli.
He also serves Nayman.
Is he so?
As long as...
...such people only care about their profits
instead of helping...
...they will keep experiencing my punishment.
What shall we do now, my Bey?
We will not stop until we bury them!
Now let's come to the main question.
Orhan heard everything.
And he will tell Osman that you will go
through the location of the White Tree
That's good.
I will not take that way.
Your brain works, merchant.
You will go through Kurtagzi.
...and I...
I will be at the White Tree location.
I will kill Osman there.
Commander Nayman, Orhan knows about me.
What happens if he tells Osman?
Vizier of the supreme Seljuq state.
Are you afraid of a Bey, huh?
When you arrive in Konya.
Osman will be dead.
Commander Nayman, what mission
aer you giving me in Konya?
You will behead Sultan Aladdin.
And you will hang it on
the highest place in Konya
There will be no one left to prevent this.
The seal will come and
we will establish the state
Tell me, son.
How did you get out of there?
They were carrying goods, my Bey.
I hid among them.
So...
Wasn't there a soldier guarding you?
No, my Bey.
Son.
So you didn't run away from there.
They let you go.
So what you heard is suspicious.
Are you saying that
what Orhan heard was a lie?
No, the traitors are known.
...the traitors are known, however...
The location of the white tree must be a trap.
They want to drag us there.
But we will hit them where they least expect it.
We will set such an ambush that...
Do you mean I have failed
in my mission, my Bey?
No, you have done your job perfectly.
If Nayman hadn't called you in,
our plan would have been obvious.
And if you had not gotten out...
there would have been 500 horsemen
waiting for you in front of the headquarters.
Son, you went and saw.
Now it is time to defeat him.
Thank you, my Bey.
How do we defeat them, my Bey?
We will suffer very heavy losses in
any war we wage in the field.
For this reason, we will launch
another campaign against them.
Is it a secret, my Bey?
The secret will be revealed
when the time comes.
Son, tell me, how is your hand?
It's fine, father.
What he did was beneficial, thank Allah.
Thank Allah.
Now let's cut to the main problem.
Now it's time for
Aktemur and Alcicek to tie the knot.
Do the preparations.
Enter all of Bayindir's
secret warehouses and stores.
I will set the seal on this matter.
Will you let me in, Mother Sultan?
Enter!
It's from Osman Bey, ma'am.
Osman bey calls me to
Yenisehir at dawn.
He says it is important.
What are you planning again, Osman?
- Do you accept?
- I do.
Aktemur, Gunduz Bey's son...
Will you marry Alcicek, daughter
of Oktem Bey, with the dowry you promised her?
Yes.
- Do you accept?
- I do.
And you witnesses, do you bear witness to this?
- We do.
We do.
May Allah bless your future.
- Amen.
Oh my Allah, we witnessed
the marriage of these two young people.
You shall testify.
Bless their marriage.
- Amen.
Grant this couple understanding,
love and stability in their marriage
- Amen.
Do not create a place for misunderstanding,
hatred or separation between them.
- Amen.
Al-Fatiha
In the name of Allah,
the most gracious, the most merciful
Son.
This was for my brother, the martyr, Gunduz Bey.
I put it in your trust now.
Take it.
In the name of Allah,
the most gracious, the most merciful
Alps!
Draw your swords!
Your command, my Bey!
What did Aktemur Bey do?
He held wedding and banquet
What did he do for Alcicek Hatun?
He slaughtered calfs
and sheep for her
Did he break a heart or say a bad word?
He did neither break hearts
nor say a bad word
And he married to Alcicek Hautn!
So, Allah bless them
Amen
May you both be happy!
Sleep on one pillow!
You stop, you stop.
Brother stop here.
- Let's do it.
Strike, Gurbuz Alp!
Come on!
You are next, Cerkutay.
He will see marriage in his dreams.
I heard, I heard,
but this time you bumped into a solid rock!
What a rock huh!
Look, he can't even stand
without his shield!
Alps!
Stop!
Stop.
Don't do this.
Come to your senses.
Go rest, there's a war tomorrow!
We are in difficulty!
Alps!
What is this lunatic doing here?
Lunatic?
Who?
I'm lunatic! I am!
She's talking about our lunatic, Cerkutay!
He's roaming here thanks to
the mercy of Osman bey.
We give him some soup
and send him away.
Get out of my way.
He's very coward.
Stop it, don't be afraid, I'll look at your head.
Stop.
Good, good.
I hit you well, bless my hands.
Ulgen!
Yes mother?
Give this lunatic oinment.
I will.
If I'd known he was a lunatic,
I wouldn't have hit him.
Lunatic, lunatic, lunatic!
You did well, very well.
Look, he came to his senses.
He is blooming.
Let me kiss your hand.
What tribe are you from?
- I?
- Yes!
I am from...
Are you married?
Married?
Mother, mother come on,
let's take you to your room
Let's go.
-Is she her mother?
-Yes
Brother.
Look.
You've crossed many obstacles
in your life, Cerkutay.
But now you are in a very
difficult position, brother.
Yes I am, I am doomed.
I can't walk around without a shield anymore.
What happened to the double swords, Cerkutay?
The mansion has become
more dangerous than the battlefield.
May Allah help me.
Allah helps the lunatic, brother.
I've had enough of you!
Enough of you!
Yenisehir
That Nayman... his name is Nayman, right?
If the place he mentioned to Bayindir
is a trap, so are we going twords a trap?
What's it, brother?
Are you afraid, Cerkutay.
Let me ask you,
have you ever seen Cerkutay scared?
If we hadn't seen that you were afraid of
the brown midwife, we would have believed it
I doubt the mind of those who are not afraid of it
Don't mention her name in front of me
By Allah , brother, if only that
brown midwife had hit you a little harder
I would be in a worse position than,
Allah forbid, the lunatic you imitated
Look at the warriors, at the warriors
Look at their tongues
Your mouths do more work than your hands
Boran Alp didn't take care of you while I was
a spy in Ingol, brothers
How did I not take care of them, brother?
Also, wasn't Osman Bey saying
We're notorious for intrigue,
didn't he say that?
That means he said it at a time when
you weren't listening, Cerkutay.
Brother, brother, I do not hear.
I pray that no one will sign your tongues.
Brother, really, what are we going to do?
And I don't know, brother
But I know we're going to
hit Nayman hard.
powerful hit.
Yes, big hit
Warriors!
Dear brothers!
Brave ones!
We will unite!
And we will unite.
Then that Nayman--
-Nayman, isn't it?
-Yes.
We're going to hit Nayman hard!
Attention, Osman Bey!
Warriors, heroes!
If you are going to fight
soldiers from hell...
Then you should not allow them
to enter heaven.
But we will do the opposite.
Close the doors.
Line up the spears.
You will set traps everywhere.
You'll put explosives everywhere.
We'll root Nayman out of
our heavenly home.
Come on, everyone spread out
all over Yenişehir.
Your command, sir.
Yes sir.
My lord!
The Queen Mother is coming
Come on.
Come on, everyone back to work.
Forgive me, Great Commander Nayman.
You don't deserve forgiveness, blacksmith.
But we'll see...
if your sword is sharp,
you will die quickly.
If not...
Forgive me, Great Commander Neiman.
Pardon me.
Forgive me, Great Commander Nayman.
How will I defeat the enemy with
his likes...
which is not doing its job properly?
He will pay with his life.
Take that sword.
I will slowly decapitate Osman with it.
Osman is now walking toward
the trap I set for him.
This will end today.
After the fall of Osman,
everything will be as I want.
The blood that will be spilled on
this earth will serve our purpose.
Draw your swords.
Ride the horses.
We're going to the site of the White Tree
to behead Osman.
Today is the day of Arlik Khan's wrath.
Arlik Khan! Arlik Khan!
This time isn't like the times we went to
Sogut, nor the times we went to Ingol.
Check the chariots and men well now.
Our way is long.
We have to be ready.
Everything is ready, sir.
Warriors are very strong.
We took with us the strongest
and most dexterous of them.
Good. Good.
The road ahead is very long, Hussein.
We'll go from here now...
but our return will be very different.
You will see that I open one court and
close another in Yenişehir Palace.
It suits you, sir, it suits you very much.
Definitely befitting.
Come on, hurry up, come on.
Get the horses quick, come on.
Warriors, come on.
They spent all day at camp .
Then they began collecting goods
before the call to prayer.
Look at his condition.
Walk with a little more pride,
Bayindir Bey.
The time will surely come.
And we'll quell your arrogance, too.
My mission ends here, Turgut Bey.
I have to go back to Osman Bey's side,
may Allah help you.
May Allah help us all, my brother.
Thank you.
What shall we do now, sir?
What are you thinking?
Let this fox out on the road...
There's definitely something
I'm thinking of.
Shall we hit him and leave him?
No.
First, we will observe him as
his shadow step by step
And then he will bring that
precious seal to us with his feet.
Alright, sir.
Your time is now, Bayindir.
Since when do the elders come to
the younger, Osman Bey?
You summoned me.
If you were come to hold me accountable
you would come without thinking that.
What is the reason for
the preparations outside?
It is for the doom of the infidels.
Never worry.
Tell me without further ado,
Osman Bey.
Vizier Saveli.
He's been working for Commander Nayman
since day one.
Grand Vizier of the House of Seljuk!
How could this happen?
While I was at headquarters that day...
even your closest soldiers kneeled
before Nayman
You've seen that.
Never be surprised by Vizie Saveli.
My son?
Vizier Savel is the closest
person to Sultan Aladdin.
The Sultan's life is in danger.
I will go to Konya without
wasting time, Osman Bey.
Stop.
You are right.
Konya and Sultan
Alaeddin are also in danger.
But if you go, you'll be in danger too.
And what do you advise me, Osman Bey?
(Oktam tribe)
welcome
You were welcome and you were easy
Welcome!
You both came at the right time.
My daughter.
My son.
Welcome to your home.
I have prepared your tent.
There is nothing missing for you anymore.
Tent?
And where did you get this from?
They'll stay at the palace, Bengu Hatun.
They came here to kiss your hand.
What's going on, Bengu Hatun?
Tell us what you want to say now.
Aktemur lives in the palace.
And the place Alcicek is with her husband.
Or are you thinking of something
we don't know about?
There's nothing to hide,
I said what I wanted from the start
Isn't it, son?
What's going on, Aktemur?
You will not go alone, Queen Mother
We'll go together
I will never forget the one who got me
through the hard times, Bala Hatun.
May Allah bless you.
We also wanted someone to support us in
difficult times, not the other way around.
We also do not forget, Sultana Mother
But today is a day for unity.
We have to go without
wasting any more time.
May Allah bless you, Osman Bey.
May Allah make your way easy,
Sultana Mother
Bala.
Saveli realizes that Orhan
knows he's a traitor.
And that we go there as enemies.
For this reason, you should be careful.
Don't worry, my dear Osman,
and you, too, be careful.
Say that we will fight the infidels
with our swords together.
They will not leave us alone.
We will not stop fighting them either.
May Allah bless our battle..
We will return victorious.
And we will see your victory when
we return too, Allah willing.
May Allah make your path easy.
Bengu Hatun.
Why did the beys gather?
A meeting will be held to select the bey.
Today I will hand over the position to the
lord of the Kargin tribe.
And my son-in-law Aktemur
will be made lord of the Kargin tribe.
And he will receive Öktem's trust.
Say something, Aktemur.
Bengi Hatun...
Mother Bengi wants this.
And I learned that from Alcicek yesterday.
But I haven't made up my mind yet.
What are you knitting again, Bengi Hatun?
How could you do this
without Osman Bey's knowledge?
Isn't everything we've lived enough?
No game, Aunt Malhun.
My mother will hand over
my father's trust to Aktemur.
What is the point of being
angry about this?
Also, why would Osman Bey object?
So, you're okay with that
too, Alcicek?
How quickly you forgot what your
mother did, my daughter
Don't you guys have brains, Aktemur?
Ladies!
This is my tribe, watch your words
and don't raise your voice!
My husband is a martyr, which game
are you talking about?
Beys are in a hurry to hold
the inauguration ceremony.
And I have nothing to hide from Osman Bey.
We're not going to ask you when we want to
raise our voices, Bengi Hatun.
It's all been a game of yours,
how can this be free of it?
You both insisted there was a game
What game is this? I make my son-in-law
the master of my tribe
Do you distrust me or Aktemur?
Aktemur will do exactly what is
required of him
I trust him fully.
But I am not satisfied with
this matter, my daughter.
And this is my final word to you, Aktemur.
Aktemur, we trust you more
than anyone else.
But we are not satisfied with this.
Beys.
Go to the tent.
I'm coming.
The meeting will begin.
Make up your mind, Aktemur.
If you say you will receive the trust...
the meeting is here.
If you refuse it...
the door is in that direction.
Come on.
Let's not leave the beys waiting.
Alcicek, come on, my daughter.
Mother.
My uncle's wife.
Why do you object so much to this?
Aktemur.
I am not satisfied with this.
You will not sit on that position.
Your mother's right, Aktemur.
Trusting Bengii and sitting
in that position...
You will only harm yourself.
Osman, he should have been here.
Did he understand that it was a trap?
Osman!
Send soldiers
to all directions!
No one will come back until
you find Osman!
If you don't find Osman,
I will take your souls
You thought you were a wolf,
and you thought we were sheep
War in my homeland is not a game.
Claws are not enough to be a wolf,
you need brains.
You are missing both, and your
end is near.
This letter...
It's your death sentence, Osman.
Even if I hid well...
Even if you go down seven
layers underground...
You will not be able to escape from me.
I will destroy Yenişehir
over Osman's head.
Get ready, come on!
Osman wants to lure you
into a trap, Commander Nayman!
Trap? What trap can stand before me?
I am the lion who pulled the arrows
out of his body with his teeth.
I will destroy Yenişehir.
Swords will not be sheathed until
none of Osman's descendants remain.
Come on!
Sit down.
Boran.
What's the situation?
We've evacuated all the houses, my bey.
And we've transported the
people safely to Ingol.
And all the brave ones
whose hands carry arms with us.
We put gunpowder on every street, my bey.
They are ready to tear
the infidels to shreds.
Thank you. Thank you.
Will you permit me to enter, my bey?
Come on, Konur.
Sir, as per your orders,
I was with Bayindir.
I gave the job to Turgut to come here.
Thank you. Come.
Now.
Turgut and the heroes with him...
They'll use Bayindir and take the seal.
And the Sultana Mother and Bala Hatun...
will go to Konya and destroy Saveli.
And we...
...will take care of Nayman's army.
Will he come, my Bey?
If he does not come after
my words...
It means that he is smart enough to
defeat his anger.
But people like Nayman
rely on their own strength.
His anger and arrogance
will inevitably overcome him.
So he will come.
Now, gather here.
Come on.
Most importantly...
Their first target will be our mansion.
For this reason,
you will place archers on rooftops.
in these places...
Then...
My sons...
Come closer and listen to me well.
Aladdin, Orhan
Soldiers who will try to enter from here...
You will drive them back with your arrows.
Do you understand, sons?
Your command, my Bey.
Thank you.
The command is yours, my Bey.
And for us...
The rest of the Mongol soldiers
will be in the field.
We will drag them to the places where
we have previously put the gunpowder.
When the soldiers are pushed back...
Baysungur, Aykurt.
You will light the gunpowder on both sides.
Even if they run away from the fire...
They will not be able to
escape from the boiling oils
Okay, my Bey.
Let's see how high
the Mongol soldiers can fly.
Mongol soldiers are like birds, my Bey.
Yes, yes.
He who harbors anger accompanies death.
Come to me, Nayman.
Nobody's coming,
who are we waiting for, Bengi Hatun?
Where is the Bey you said you'd bring?
I don't think Bey is coming.
So, we will choose our own Bey.
Right, Beys?
- Yes, we can.
- That's right.
He is right.
Mother.
He won't come.
He made a choice.
We will take care of ourselves.
This is not the time to stand idly,
we have to choose
Beys!
As the new Bey of the Kargin tribe...
I nominate my son-in-law
Aktemur, Gunduz Bey's son.
If anyone objects...
Speak now.
You recommend Aktemur in order to...
...keep us captive under Kayis!
What captivity are you talking about?
Hasn't Kayi been fighting for
generations for your freedom?
What do you accuse of those who offer their blood
so that you do not fall into captivity!
It's not an accusation, it's the truth
Do you know what the truth is?
You no longer have a place in this meeting.
Who are you to kick me out of here?
I am the Bey of Kargin tribe!
Get lost!
Bless your Beyship, Aktemur Bey.
So...
Now...
The sword is yours, the throne is yours.
And the Kargin tribe is yours.
Kutlu!
I hand over the trust to its owner.
Do you witness, Beys?
Yes.
- Do you witness, Beys?
- Yes!
Your entrust is my entrust.
And your children are my children.
And your soul is my soul.
Now that you trust me...
And you accepted me as your Bey...
I will sacrifice my life on your way.
Shall be blessed.
Let's see.
O Allah
O Right!
Allah is the greatest!
Come to me.
O Right!
Come on, you dogs!
Split up!
You dogs.
O Allah!
Oh Right!
Alps!
Getting out of Yenişehir is not that simple
Come on, O Allah!
Allah is the greatest!
Sir, we killed a few of them
but there are many waiting for us outside
How long is left for iftar, Hussein?
It's still early, my Bey.
We got hungry!
Yes my Bey, we got hungry.
Let's take that seal, Hussein.
And then our age will begin, I hope so.
It will begin, my Bey, it will begin.
It's a trap, alps!
Where is Bayindir going like this?
And I was wondering if
the infidels were the ones blocking our way!
What's it, Turgut Bey?
Have you come to spill the blood of your brothers?
Not at all, not the blood of the brother,
but I will spill the blood of the ignoble!
Haven't you seen this coming?
Did you think we wouldn't hold you
accountable after all the betrayal?
Get out of my way and
I will forgive you for what you said.
No need to do that.
You're exposed.
You work with
Nayman, and everyone knows it.
This means that Osman
was not deceived by all this.
Yes.
Know that I will not give up.
That's not going to help
you, Bayındır, what are you going to do?
I will say for once, you have
no way out of here.
You are all prisoners and your
convoy is our property.
It's not that easy, Turgut.
Come here.
I bear witness that there is no
deity but Allah...
and I bear witness that Muhammad
is His servant and Messenger.
In the name of Allah, the most
gracious, the most merciful.
Not yet.
We need you.
Stand up.
But you're going to do something you
know this time, you're going to betray Nayman.
And then you'll give us that very
valuable seal.
Kutan, tie him to the back of the cart.
Your command, my Bey.
Come on.
Konya Palace
Celali, find Vizier Saveli.
We will find my son, Bala Hatun.
Come on then.
Mother Sultan.
Vizier Saveli knows we're coming.
Let's split our forces to find Sultan
Aladdin as soon as possible.
This is very dangerous, Bala Hatun.
We have no other solution, Mother Sultan.
The only power that will stop Saveli
is the power of Sultan Aladdin.
Be careful.
Okay.
May our conquest be blessed.
Alps!
Sisters.
Bala Hatun.
To whom is the intention and
to whom is the share?
I was waiting for Mother Sultan.
Don't worry, Saveli.
Either she kills you or I do.
Where is the Sultan Aladdin?
- If he's hurt...
- He is.
I'll give his head as a gift to Nayman.
But you won't even see it.
When the lion enters the trap,
then even the foxes become strong.
Move to cut off your heads.
Time has passed.
I am the lion and I am the wolf.
Attack!
Everybody, get ready! We'll get
in when we get the news.
There are horsemen
coming, Commander Nayman.
Soldiers, get ready.
Blood, blood, blood!
Nayman.
Are you hiding behind your soldiers?
Why don't you appear in front of me?
You defended your city...
and you killed my soldiers.
You must be tired.
But what about me?
I'm just angry.
I will kill you.
And I have my faith.
Will this protect you from my wrath?
Your anger will be your end.
I will show you the
last drop of my mercy.
We will not shed blood anymore.
It's the last blood, Osman.
Say it.
Tomorrow at sunset, you will come
to the site of the Karaoluk.
You and I only.
We'll go out to the arena.
Only one of us will make it out alive.
Last blood, Osman.
Okay.
When I show up at the arena, it
will be mine when I draw my sword.
I accept that.
Your soldiers will leave my
lands when I kill you.
Tell your Beys.
You will obey!
When I kill you, you won't even
have a grave in those lands.
Visit our website for more: turkision.com